

Applicant for:

# PHP Developer (PHP, JavaScript, AWS)

Starboard Asia Co.,ltd. 28 August 2021

## **Tran Hai Nam**

Main interests: PHP, Laravel

What skills, work projects or achievements make you a strong candidate for this position?

Note from ITviec: Tran Hai Nam skipped the cover letter.

# Nam Tran Hai

Date of birth: 20.04.1977

Gender: Male

Address: Ap Dong 1, Thoi Tam Thon, Hoc Mon, Ho Chi

Minh City.

Phone: 0909 554 754

Email: myducnam@gmail.com

Skype: ybt.nam

## **SUMMARY**

After my graduation in 2004, I have been working as a PHP Developer for over 15 years.

I have been working hardly, quickly, efficiently.

I know how to know build up a teamwork, how to support other people in team.

I can both work alone and teamwork.

### **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of IT from University of Natural Science, 2000 – 2004

#### **SKILLS**

#### **CMS**

## Drupal 7/8, Wordpress, Magento, Opencart, Zencart, SugarCRM

#### PHP FRAMEWORK

Laravel, CakePHP, Symfony, Codelgniter

#### DATABASE

## **SOURCE MANAGEMENT**

Mysql, MongoDB, PostgreSQL

GIT, Gitblab

#### **PROJECT MANAGEMENT**

#### **OTHER**

Jira, Redmine

Template engine: Twig, Smarty, Memcache, Redis Composer, Docker, Vagrant, Linux, Window Javascript/Jquery/Ajax, NodeJS, HTML/CSS

#### **LANGUAGE**

Can communicate in English (but not very well, so I am trying to improve my skill)

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## SENIOR PHP DEVELOPER

## DRCOM GROUP

2016 - present

Develop and maintain site with Drupal 7/8, Wordpress, Laravel, Symfony, Javascript/Jquery

Websites:
cyendiv.com
trajenta.com
xovoltib.com
jardiance.in
laverandaresort
s.com

## SENIOR PHP DEVELOPER

## DMS Company

2016 – 2011

Develop and maintain site with CMS: Joomla, Wordpress

E-commerce platform:
Opencart,
Magento,
OSCommerce

Realtime app: NodeJS/PHP/Mys

ql

Penny auction site

## SENIOR PHP DEVELOPER

## NCS Company

2011-2007

Develop site with PHP, Joomla, OSCommerce, Zencart

#### PHP DEVELOP

Knowledge Software Company

2007 - 2004

Develop sites with PHP, Smarty Template Engine, Javascript